[
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_1",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $2^4$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "16",
        "latexAnswer": "16",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_1",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $3^3$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "27",
        "latexAnswer": "27",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_1",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $1^5$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_2",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $8^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_2",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $\\sqrt{567}^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_2",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(-12380910923)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_3",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(\\frac{3}{5})^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "5/3",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{5}{3}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_3",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(\\frac{3}{4})^{-2}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "16/9",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{16}{9}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "questions_3",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(6)^{-2}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/36",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{36}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
        {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(5)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(3)^{-2}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/9",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{9}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(7)^1$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "7",
        "latexAnswer": "7",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(2)^3$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "8",
        "latexAnswer": "8",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(4)^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/4",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{4}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(9)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(\\frac{1}{2})^{-2}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "4",
        "latexAnswer": "4",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(\\frac{4}{5})^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "5/4",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{5}{4}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(10)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(3)^{-3}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/27",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{27}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(2)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(5)^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/5",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{5}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(7)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(9)^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/9",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{9}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(4)^3$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "64",
        "latexAnswer": "64",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(6)^0$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1",
        "latexAnswer": "1",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(8)^{-2}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/64",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{64}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(3)^2$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "9",
        "latexAnswer": "9",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(2)^{-4}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/16",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{16}",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Rozwiąż $(10)^{-1}$",
        "answerForEvaluation": "1/10",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{10}",
        "explanation": ""
    }
]